rupeebot.com 2013-09-10

# Rupeebot | Privacy & Cookie Policy

Our Policies are derived from the policies of Slickdeals.net & Hotukdeals.com

Rupeebot.com is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. Although we will do our utmost to protect your information, we cannot guarantee the security of the data you submit to our website or our app; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures to try to prevent unauthorised access.  

We will never pass on information about you unless we are legally obliged to do so. We will never use any of your data in ways that have unjustified adverse effects on you.

Rupeebot.com contains links to third party stores and websites. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites have their own privacy policies and are not affiliated with Rupeebot.com. It is your responsibility to check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside India. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will do our best and take all reasonable steps to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

**Emails and Correspondence**

Rupeebot.com offers support through a third party provider which is located at www.rupeebot.ticksy.com. When submitting a support request, you are provided an option of submitting a public or a private ticket.

**Commenting on the site**

You can delete any posts you make across Rupeebot.com at any time. If you are not able to and wish to delete, please contact support with your request. You are wholly responsible for what you post on the site. We advise against posting personal information or pictures or anything that could identify you as an individual on Rupeebot.com. We recommend not using sensitive information when creating usernames; you’re responsible for ensuring you keep your sign in information private.

**IP Addresses and Cookies**

As is common practice with almost all professional websites this site uses cookies, which are tiny files that are downloaded to your computer, to improve your experience. This page describes what information we gather, how we use it and why we sometimes need to store these cookies. We will also share how you can prevent these cookies from being stored however this may downgrade or 'break' certain elements of the sites functionality.

This cookies policy constitutes the agreement between you ("User") and Magus Digital Media Private Limited ("Company") and its services including but not limited to, RupeeBot and RupeeBot.com ("Site").

We may collect information about your IP address in order to maintain a safe environment for our users. We may analyse details of your visits to our site or your use of the app, including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data and other communication data and the resources that you access.

We may obtain information about your usage of the website or the app by using a cookie file.

Websites use cookies to make the browsing experience more efficient, and to help you use websites to their full potential. Cookies are a small text file that is transferred to your hard drive or the internal memory of your mobile device.

**What do our cookies do?**

  * They help you to personalise your experience with our site, allowing you to engage with the Rupeebot.com community fully. Our cookies enable you to vote, comment, like and promote comments and stay signed in while you browse the site.
  * They ensure your sign up process is as efficient as possible, we use cookies as a way to authenticate you as a registered user, allowing you to fully personalise your user profile and settings, including local deals location.
  * They allow us to track affiliate activity. Some merchants pay commission when you go to their site from Rupeebot.com.
  * Our cookies do not share any of your personal data with us, and we would never use any information derived from cookies to try to identify anybody. We will never share any data with third parties.

By using Rupeebot.com, you agree to the guidelines set out in our privacy policy. If you want to find out more about cookies or if you want to know how to delete or control the cookies that are stored on your computer you can visit AboutCookies.org

**Third Party Cookies**

In some special cases we may use cookies provided by trusted third parties. The following section details which third party cookies you might encounter through this Site.

This Site may use Google Analytics which is one of the most widespread and trusted analytics solution on the web for helping us to understand how you use the site and ways that we can improve your experience. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site and the pages that you visit so we can continue to produce engaging content.

Third party analytics are used to track and measure usage of this site so that we can continue to produce engaging content. These cookies may track things such as how long you spend on the site or pages you visit which help us to understand how we can improve the site for you.

From time to time we may test new features and make subtle changes to the way that the site is delivered. When we are still testing new features these cookies may be used to ensure that you receive a consistent experience whilst on the site whilst ensuring we understand which optimisations our users appreciate the most.

The Google AdSense service we use to serve advertising uses a DoubleClick cookie to serve more relevant ads across the web and limit the number of times that a given ad is shown to you.

We may use adverts to offset the costs of running this site and provide funding for further development. The behavioural advertising cookies used by this site are designed to ensure that we provide you with the most relevant adverts where possible by anonymously tracking your interests and presenting similar things that may be of interest.

In some cases we may provide you with custom content based on what you tell us about yourself either directly or indirectly by linking a social media account. These types of cookies simply allow us to provide you with content that we feel may be of interest to you.

Several partners may advertise on our behalf and affiliate tracking cookies simply allow us to see if our customers have come to the site through one of our partner sites so that we can credit them appropriately and where applicable allow our affiliate partners to provide any bonus that they may provide you for making a purchase.

We also may use social media buttons and/or plugins on this site that allow you to connect with your social network in various ways. For these to work the following social media sites including but not limited to; Facebook, Twitter will set cookies through our site which may be used to enhance your profile on their site or contribute to the data they hold for various purposes outlined in their respective privacy policies.

**Disabling Cookies**

You can prevent the setting of cookies by adjusting the settings on your browser (see your browser Help for how to do this). Be aware that disabling cookies will affect the functionality of this and many other websites that you visit. Disabling cookies will usually result in also disabling certain functionality and features of this site. We also reserve the right to discontinue any or all services provided if your browser declines cookies. This is to assure all users have read and accept the Cookie Policy for our Site Therefore it is recommended that you do not disable cookies.

**Changes to this privacy policy**

Magus Digital Media Private Limited the company that operates Rupeebot.com has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page,. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. **Contact**

Questions, comments and requests regarding this policy are welcomed and should be addressed via the support centre located at www.rupeebot.ticksy.com. If you require a full list of all the cookies we use, please put in a request through the Support Centre.
